Thank you, Bob. Mr Chris Jim of Partie from our office?
Emily Fatherweller thankful for You were grateful
For the way that Love is and provide force in come an end to Independence Day
We're thankful
The men & women who are willing To serve Our Country
And protectOur Freedom Together here
Be a part Of Our Government Lordess
Be with us tonight decisions made will be according
Your Will it's on your name we pray Amen
I play the religious dispute with why have been a non-sate of America.
And it's very, really relevant for which are things one nation under an individual would be able to achieve in justice as well?
All right but we can put on scheduled personal chances five claims list most true proof
Is that double high?
Six minutes from June 20th 2023 regular meeting
Most true proof
723-26 for sitting and expanding water waste our wastewater collection Oklahoma Water Resource Board loan proceeds
So we have a lone with OWRB it's reimbursable loans so as We spend that.
We're drawing it down so we are not getting interest ahead of our work.
So this is one those times would you make motion to a brief second?
Parker five, he said double pie
Hey Carpenter associates engagement letter for accounting services in the fiscal year 2324
So this is a revision of the agreement that we brought before you few weeks ago
Legals had an opportunity to review it and I think they ended up changing us in one
Of these sentences, but should be ready
You know what's going on?
It was all determination
I actually looked for the exact sitting because i thought you might ask me that to
It was
The last sentence
Page four provide further both parties reserved right
To earlier terminate this engagement by giving written 60 days notice
Second
All right
New business of any which is the reason it's supposed to be this agenda
T and trusty community announcements 11 a German motion second
Okay